Guide to the Harry Adams Photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Harry Adams photographs
1943-1985
1951-1985
WA Photos 589
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
7.71
19 boxes
Photographs prints created and collected by Harry Adams, 1943-1985, that chiefly document events, activities, and individuals related to the African American community in the Los Angeles metropolitan area of California and his career as a professional photographer as well as his work for African American newspapers including the California Eagle and Los Angeles Sentinel.
Adams, Harry, 1918-1985
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from William Reese Co. on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2015.
Arrangement
Organized into three series: I. Identified Subjects, 1951-1985. II. Unidentified Subjects, 1951-1985. III. Collected Photographs, 1943-1985.
Harry Adams (1918-1985)
Harry Holden Adams, also known as "One Shot Harry," was an African American professional photographer in Los Angeles, California. He was born in Arkansas, the eldest child of Hunter Adams (1896-1966) and Robbie Lee Evans Adams (1897-1967) and brother to Hunter Havlin Adams (1920-2002) and Katherleen Norris Adams King (1923-2004). The Adams family moved to Southern California when Adams was three years old and initially settled in La Habra. Three years later they moved to Santa Ana, where his mother and extended family helped establish the Johnson Chapel African Methodist Episcopal Church. Adams attended Santa Ana College and studied music and political science.
In 1939, he married Marjorie Harris Adams (born circa 1921) and they had a son, Harry Holden Adams, Jr. (born 1939) and daughter, Theresa Lenore Adams Devillae (1941-1991); they later divorced and Adams married Lorraine Proctor in 1956. He worked as a janitor for the Santa Ana Recreation and Park Department and attended Whittier College. In August 1944, Adams was drafted in the United States Army and served as a military policeman at Camp Harahan, also known as Camp Plauche, in Louisiana until his discharge at the rank of sergeant in 1946. After his military service, Adams and his family moved from Santa Ana to Los Angeles. He then graduated from the Moler Barber College in Los Angeles and worked as a security guard with Los Angeles County and then with the Los Angeles County Sheriff Department.
Around 1950, Adams attended the California School of Photography and Graphic Design and the Fred Archer School of Photography. In 1952, he resigned from the Los Angeles County Sheriff Department and opened a photographic studio at 4223 Avalon Boulevard in Los Angeles as well as an adjoining barbershop. In 1971, Adams relocated his studio to 4300 South Central Avenue and owned the Echo Barber Shop next door at the intersection of Central Avenue and 43rd Street in Los Angeles. Adams also worked as a staff photographer for African American newspapers in Los Angeles including the California Eagle and Los Angeles Sentinel. Additionally, he was a member of the Black Photography Association as well as a travel agent and a member of the African Tourist Travel Agent Association.
Adams died in from a heart attack while on a photographic assignment in Los Angeles.
Scope and Contents
Photographic prints created and collected by Harry Adams, 1943-1985, that chiefly document events, activities, and individuals related to the African American community in the Los Angeles metropolitan area of California captured in his work for African American newspapers including the California Eagle and Los Angeles Sentinel.
Photographs that document events and activities include annual concerts of the Cavalcade of Jazz at Wrigley Field in Los Angeles, 1953-1958, discrete Freedom Rallies at the Los Angeles Sports Arena on June 18, 1961, and at Wrigley Field in Los Angeles on May 26, 1963, and a Conference of the Unemployed held at Wrigley Field in Los Angeles on May 21, 1964. A few photographs document a raid by the Los Angeles Police Department on the Black Panther Party office on December 8, 1969. There are also photographs of banquets and ceremonies related to groups including National Association for the Advancement of Colored People and United Civil Rights Committee as well as informal portraits related to Grammy Awards ceremonies.
Many of the photographs and informal portraits document local and national civic leaders and politicians as well as entertainers, celebrities, and athletes. There are also photographs related to the California Angels and Los Angeles Dodgers baseball teams as well as the football teams of California State University, Long Beach, Grambling State University, and University of Southern California.
Portraits of others include members of the Adams family, including Katherleen Norris Adams King, Marjorie Harris Adams, and Robbie Lee Evans Adams. The collection also includes many photographs collected by Harry Adams of him with others.
Photographic prints in the collection predominantly measure 8 inches by 10 inches (21.4 centimeters by 28.3 centimeters) with scattered examples with smaller dimensions.
Conditions Governing Access
The Harry Adams Photographs are the physical property of the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University. Literary rights, including copyright, belong to the authors or their legal heirs and assigns. For further information, consult the appropriate curator.
California eagle; Los Angeles sentinel; African American photographers -- California -- Pictorial works; African Americans -- California -- Pictorial works; African Americans -- California -- Los Angeles -- Pictorial works; Athletes -- California -- Pictorial works; Athletes -- California -- Los Angeles -- Pictorial works; Baseball players -- California -- Pictorial works; Baseball players -- California -- Los Angeles -- Pictorial works; Celebrities -- California -- Pictorial works; Celebrities -- California -- Los Angeles -- Pictorial works; Civic leaders -- California -- Pictorial works; Civic leaders -- California -- Los Angeles -- Pictorial works; Entertainers -- California -- Pictorial works; Entertainers -- California -- Los Angeles -- Pictorial works; Football players -- California -- Pictorial works; Football players -- California -- Los Angeles -- Pictorial works; Politicians -- California -- Pictorial works; Politicians -- California -- Los Angeles -- Pictorial works; California -- Pictorial works; Los Angeles (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Los Angeles Metropolitan Area (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Wrigley Field (Los Angeles, Calif.) -- Pictorial works; Gelatin silver prints; Photographic prints; Photographs; Aaron, Hank, 1934- -- Portraits; Adams family -- Portraits; Adams, Harry, 1918-1985; Adams, Harry, 1918-1985 -- Portraits; Adams, Marjorie Harris, approximately 1921- -- Portraits; Adams, Neile -- Portraits; Adams, Robbie Lee Evans, 1897-1967 -- Portraits; Ali, Muhammad, 1942-2016 -- Portraits; Allen, Steve, 1921-2000 -- Portraits; Amos, John, 1939-; Armstrong, Louis, 1901-1971 -- Portraits; Baldwin, James, 1924-1987 -- Portraits; Barty, Billy -- Portraits; Belafonte, Harry, 1927- -- Portraits; Benny, Jack, 1894-1974 -- Portraits; Berle, Milton, 1908-2002 -- Portraits; Blue, Vida, 1949- -- Portraits; Bono, Sonny -- Portraits; Bradley, Ethel Arnold, 1919-2008 -- Portraits; Bradley, Tom, 1917-1998 -- Portraits; Brando, Marlon, 1924-2004 -- Portraits; Brooke, Edward W. (Edward William), 1919-2015 -- Portraits; Brookins, H. H. (Hamel Hartford), 1925-2012 -- Portraits; Brown, Edmund G. (Edmund Gerald), 1905-1996 -- Portraits; Brown, James, 1933-2006 -- Portraits; Brown, Jerry, 1938- -- Portraits; Brown, Jim, 1936- -- Portraits; Brown, Roger, 1937- -- Portraits; Brown, Willie L., Jr. (Willie Lewis), 1934- -- Portraits; Browne, Roscoe Lee -- Portraits; Bunche, Ralph J. (Ralph Johnson), 1904-1971 -- Portraits; Burke, Yvonne Brathwaite -- Portraits; Burr, Raymond, 1917-1993 -- Portraits; Caesar, Adolph, 1933-1986 -- Portraits; Calloway, Cab, 1907-1994 -- Portraits; Calloway, Zulme, 1915-2008 -- Portraits; Campanella, Roy, 1921-1993 -- Portraits; Campbell, Glen, 1936-2017 -- Portraits; Carter, Jimmy, 1924- -- Portraits; Carter, Rosalynn, 1927- -- Portraits; Cato, Jim; Charles, Ray, 1930-2004 -- Portraits; Cher, 1946 -- Portraits; Cochran, Johnnie, 1937-2005 -- Portraits; Cole, Nat King, 1919-1965 -- Portraits; Cosby, Bill, 1937- -- Portraits; Crawford, Willie, 1946-2004 -- Portraits; Crosby, Bing, 1903-1977 -- Portraits; Damone, Vic -- Portraits; Davis, Sammy, Jr., 1925-1990 -- Portraits; Davis, Tommy, 1939- -- Portraits; Davis, Willie, 1940-2010 -- Portraits; De Lory, Al -- Portraits; Derek, Bo -- Portraits; Diller, Phyllis -- Portraits; DiMaggio, Joe, 1914-1999 -- Portraits; Drysdale, Don, 1936-1993 -- Portraits; Durante, Jimmy, 1893-1980 -- Portraits; Dymally, Mervyn M., 1926-2012 -- Portraits; Ellington, Duke, 1899-1974 -- Portraits; Engle, Clair, 1911-1964 -- Portraits; Falk, Peter, 1927-2011 -- Portraits; Ferrell, F. Douglas (Frederick Douglas), 1915-1982 -- Portraits; Foreman, George, 1949- -- Portraits; Foreman, Percy Eugene, 1902- -- Portraits; Foxx, Betty Jean Harris -- Portraits; Foxx, Redd, 1922-1991 -- Portraits; Garner, James -- Portraits; Gates, Daryl F., 1926-2010 -- Portraits; Gilliam, Jim, 1928-1978 -- Portraits; Gipson-Penland, Gertrude -- Portraits; Gordy, Berry -- Portraits; Hackett, Buddy, 1924-2003 -- Portraits; Hahn, Kenneth -- Portraits; Haley, Alex, 1921-1992 -- Portraits; Hawkins, Augustus F. -- Portraits; Hayes, Isaac -- Portraits; Heston, Charlton -- Portraits; Hudson, Elbert T., 1921-1917 -- Portraits; Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978 -- Portraits; Johnson, Davey -- Portraits; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973 -- Portraits; Jones, Deacon, 1938-2013 -- Portraits; Kennedy, Edward M. (Edward Moore), 1932-2009 -- Portraits; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 -- Portraits; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968 -- Portraits; King, B. B. -- Portraits; King, Coretta Scott, 1927-2006 -- Portraits; King, Don, 1931- -- Portraits; King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1929-1968 -- Portraits; Koufax, Sandy, 1935- -- Portraits; Laine, Frankie, 1913-2007 -- Portraits; Lawford, Peter, 1923-1984 -- Portraits; Leonard, Sugar Ray, 1956- -- Portraits; Lindsay, Gilbert, 1900-1990 -- Portraits; Lloyd, Charles E. (Charles Earl) -- Portraits; Louis, Joe, 1914-1981 -- Portraits; Lundy, Lamar, 1935-2007 -- Portraits; Martin, Dean, 1917-1995 -- Portraits; Mastin, Will, 1878-1979 -- Portraits; Mathis, Johnny -- Portraits; Mays, Willie, 1931- -- Portraits; McCormick, Larry, 1933-2004 -- Portraits; McQueen, Steve, 1930-1980 -- Portraits; Meadows, Jayne, 1919-2015 -- Portraits; Meredith, James, 1933- -- Portraits; Miles, Rosalind -- Portraits; Miller, Loren -- Portraits; Mills, Billy, 1929- -- Portraits; Mitchum, Robert -- Portraits; Montalbán, Ricardo -- Portraits; Muse, Clarence -- Portraits; Nader, Ralph, 1934- -- Portraits; Pérez, Tony, 1942- -- Portraits; Poitier, Sidney, 1927- -- Portraits; Pottios, Myron, 1939- -- Portraits; Pye, Brad, Jr., 1931- -- Portraits; Quinn, Anthony, 1915-2001 -- Portraits; Reagan, Ronald, 1911-2004 -- Portraits; Reese, Pee Wee, 1918-1999 -- Portraits; Robinson, Jackie, 1919-1972 -- Portraits; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979 -- Portraits; Rogers, Roy, 1911-1998 -- Portraits; Rolle, Esther -- Portraits; Rooney, Mickey -- Portraits; Ross, Diana, 1944- -- Portraits; Roundtree, Richard, 1942- -- Portraits; Salinger, Pierre, 1925-2004 -- Portraits; Shriver, Sargent, 1915-2011 -- Portraits; Simpson, O. J., 1947- -- Portraits; Sinatra, Frank, 1915-1998 -- Portraits; Sinatra, Nancy -- Portraits; Smith, Helen Marie Guenveur -- Portraits; Smith, Sherman W. (Sherman Wendle), 1922-2003 -- Portraits; Snider, Duke, 1926-2011 -- Portraits; Speed, Carol -- Portraits; Stengel, Casey -- Portraits; Strode, Woody -- Portraits; Sutton, Frank, 1923-1974 -- Portraits; Thomas, Danny -- Portraits; Van Dyke, Dick -- Portraits; Van Dyke, Margerie Willett, -2008 -- Portraits; Walker, Rube, 1926-1992 -- Portraits; Whyte, Leroy -- Portraits; Wilkins, Roy, 1901-1981 -- Portraits; Wills, Maury, 1932- -- Portraits; Wonder, Stevie -- Portraits; Yorty, Elizabeth, 1917-1984 -- Portraits; Yorty, Sam, 1909-1998 -- Portraits; California Angels (Baseball team) -- Portraits; California State University, Long Beach -- Pictorial works; Grambling State University -- Pictorial works; Los Angeles Dodgers (Baseball team) -- Portraits; Los Angeles Sports Arena (Los Angeles, Calif.) -- Pictorial works; University of Southern California -- Pictorial works; Cavalcade of Jazz -- Los Angeles, Calif. -- Pictorial works; William Reese Co.
- Identified Subjects, 1951–1985
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of photographic material created by Harry Adams with identified subjects or dates, 1951-1985. Many of the photographic prints have ink stamped dates on versos.
  Arrangement
  Series I is organized into 11 subseries: Adams Family; Athletes, Sports Teams, and Athletic Events; Civic Leaders, Groups, and Events; Civil Rights Leaders, Groups, and Events; Entertainers and Entertainment Events; Journalists and Authors; Judges, Attorneys, Law Enforcement; Los Angeles Personalities, Groups, and Events; Politicians and Political Events; Sites in California; and Sites and Events Outside California.
  - Adams Family
    - Exterior portrait of Katherleen Norris Adams King, Marjorie Harris Adams, and Robbie Lee Evans Adams, probably in Los Angeles, California, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Exterior view of Harry Holden Adams, Jr., and an automobile, parking lot on Avalon Boulevard, Los Angeles, California, 1953 June 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Interior view of a set dining room table in the Harry Adams family home on Thanksgiving Day, 1955 November 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Self-portrait of Harry H. Adams, 1963 July (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Athletes, Sports Teams, and Athletic Events
    Organized under headings for the main subject and then chronologically.
    - Ali, Muhammad
      - Exterior portraits of Muhammad Ali with a woman and two men, 1964 August; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Exterior and interior portraits of Muhammad Ali with groups, 1965 June 24; 8 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 6)
        Includes a portrait of Adams with Ali
      - Interior views of the audience at the boxing bout of Muhammad Ali vs Ken Norton at The Forum in Inglewood, California, which includes Redd Foxx in the audience, 1973 September 10; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - All-Star Games
      - Interior portrait of baseball players Don Drysdale of the Los Angeles Dodgers and Tony Pérez of the Cincinnati Reds after the 38th All-Star Game in Anaheim Stadium, California, 1967 July 11; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - View of Tony Pérez approaching home plate after hitting a home run during the fifteenth inning of the 38th All-Star Game at Anaheim Stadium, California, 1967 July 11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Exterior and interior views related to the 1984 Major League Baseball All-Star Game at Candlestick Park in San Francisco, California, 1984 July 10; 4 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Blue, Vida
      - Interior portrait of Vida Blue with three girls, 1971 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Jim
      - Exterior portrait of Jim Brown with a woman and two men, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Interior portrait of Jim Brown at a podium at the Los Angeles Biltmore Hotel, 1973 September (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - California Angels
      - Exterior portraits of members of the California Angels with a two men, including Brad Pye, Jr., and two women, 1966 August 28-29; 5 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Campanella, Roy
      - Exterior view of a man addressing a group at Roy Campanella Park, Compton, California, 1961 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Exterior view of Roy Campanella throwing the first pitch at Game 1 of the 1974 World Series between the Oakland Athletics and the Los Angeles Dodgers at Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles, California, with Kenneth Hahn, 1974 October 12; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - East-West Baseball Game
      - Interior portrait of Roy Campanella, Joe DiMaggio, Coretta Scott King, and others at a banquet related to the East-West Baseball Game, which benefitted the Southern Christian Leadership Conference and the Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Nonviolent Social Change, 1970 March 28; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ellis, Dock
      - Exterior portrait of Dock Ellis and another man, 1974 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Foreman, George
      - Interior and exterior portraits that include George Foreman, Don King, Larry McCormick, and others, 1974 July 21; 10 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Grambling State University Football
      - Exterior portraits of a woman, one with a Los Angeles police officer, during the football game between Grambling State University and California State University, Fullerton, at the Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum, 1971 November 27; 3 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Exterior portraits of Tom Bradley with others at a football game between Grambling State University and California State University, Long Beach, at Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum, 1973 September 8; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Views of football players during a game between Grambling State University and California State University, Long Beach, at Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum, 1973 September 8; 8 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Interior view of the broadcast booth at a football game, probably a football game between Grambling State University and California State University, Long Beach, at Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum, 1973 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Interior portrait of Redd Foxx and Betty Jean Harris Foxx during an interview, probably at a football game between Grambling State University and California State University, Long Beach, at Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum, 1973 September 8 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Hanson, Larry
      - Interior portrait of Larry Hanson, basketball coach at Thomas Jefferson High School, receiving an award from Brad Pye upon his retirement, 1973 April (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - High School Basketball
      - Interior portraits of groups of twenty men, probably members of a championship high school basketball teams or league all stars, 1973 April; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Hollywood All Stars versus Los Angeles Sports Writers baseball game
      - Views of from the annual charity baseball game featuring the Hollywood All Stars versus the Los Angeles Sports Writers, which includes Billy Barty, Don Drysdale, Phyllis Diller, Peter Falk, Sandy Koufax, Charles E. Lloyd, Mickey Rooney, Toni Lee Shelley, Nancy Sinatra, and Maury Wills, 1966 July 22; 12 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Exterior portraits related to the annual charity baseball game featuring the Hollywood All Stars versus the Los Angeles Sports Writers, including images of Billy Barty, Jack Lemmon, and Jimmy Wynn, 1974 August 2; 4 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Hollywood Stars
      - Portrait of two men wearing Hollywood Stars baseball uniforms and Albert Bluford "Rube" Walker wearing a Los Angeles Dodgers baseball uniform, 1961 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Inter-fraternal Athletics
      - Interior views of a inter-fraternal basketball tournament, including a game between members of Kappa Alpha Psi and Phi Beta Sigma, at Loyola High School, Los Angeles, 1966 May 7; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - View of female members of a drill team on a football field, probably for an event related to the Alpha Phi Alpha fraternity or a football game, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Interior portrait of ten men with awards from the Los Angeles Inter-Fraternity Basketball Tournament, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Japanese Football Association
      - Interior portrait of Tom Bradley with players from the Japanese Football Association, as well as Brad Pye, 1973 September 20 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Leonard, Sugar Ray
      - Interior portraits of Sugar Ray Leonard with others, 1985 May; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Los Angeles Dodgers
      - Interior portrait of Don Drysdale, Tommy Davis, and Sandy Koufax, with three women, circa 1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Exterior portrait of five Los Angeles Dodgers baseball players including Tommy Davis and Willie Crawford, 1964–1966 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Interior portrait of four men related to the Los Angeles Dodgers, including manager Walter Alston and Louis Brown Johnson holding his Charles Di Giovanna Memorial Trophy, 1966 February 13 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Exterior portraits of a group of four men and two women with baseball players from the Los Angeles Dodgers including Tommy Lasorda, Mike Marshall, Andy Messersmith, Jimmy Wynn, and Steve Yeager, 1974–1975; 7 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Exterior views related to a baseball game between the Los Angeles Dodgers and Houston Astros at Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles, California, including Tom Bradley throwing the first ball and a portrait of videographers, 1980 October 6; 3 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Exterior portrait of Tony Curtis wearing a Dodgers baseball uniform and a woman at Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles, California, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Exterior portrait of former Los Angeles Dodgers baseball players including Roy Campanella, Don Drysdale, Pee Wee Resse, and Duke Snider, 1984 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Los Angeles Dodgers and Other Teams
      - Exterior views related to the 1963 World Series, Game 3, between the New York Yankees and Los Angeles Dodgers at Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles, California, 1963 October 5; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - Exterior portraits and views of baseball players and others before and during the second game of the World Series between the Los Angeles Dodgers and the Baltimore Orioles at Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles, California, 1966 October 5-6; 7 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 43)
        Images includes portraits of Tommy Davis, Cary Grant, Bob Johnson, Sandy Koufax, Brooks Robinson, and Maury Wills, as well as a view of the game during the seventh inning
      - Exterior portraits of players from the Atlanta Braves and Los Angeles Dodgers, including Hank Aaron, Willie Davis, Jim Gilliam, and Earl Williams at Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles, California, 1972 September 7-8; 5 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Exterior portraits of Ethel Bradley and others with Hank Aaron and Davey Johnson of the Atlanta Braves and Walter Alston of the Los Angeles Dodgers at Dodger Stadium in Los Angeles, California, 1973 September 20; 4 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Exterior portraits of baseball players for the California Angels and Los Angeles Dodgers at a pre-season game, including Rod Carew, Reggie Jackson, and Al Oliver, as Dodger Stadium, 1985 April (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum
      - Exterior portrait of a man, probably at a football game at the Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum, 1967 October (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Los Angeles Rams
      - Exterior view of Los Angeles Rams football players on a bench during a game, including Roger Brown, Deacon Jones, Lamar Lundy, and Myron Pottios, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Louis, Joe
      - Interior portrait of Joe Louis talking on a telephone with five men, probably in a liquor store, circa 1960 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Newcombe, Don
      - View of Don Newcombe with children, 1972 June; 2 photographic prints (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Robinson, Jackie